mobyler.com 2018-05-02

# MobileVoip | Mobile Voip app for iPhone, Android and Symbian

MobileVOIP ("MobileVOIP" or "we" or "us" or "our" or other similar pronouns) takes your privacy matters very seriously. Our Privacy Policy details how we receive and use information in connection with our website located at MobileVOIP.com (the "Site"), the MobileVOIP VoIP software ("MobileVOIP App") provided on the MobileVOIP.com website (all of the foregoing, collectively, the "Services"). 

  1. **Collection and Use of Information**  
**MobileVOIP Application**  
When you install the MobileVOIP App and log in, you will be asked to allow us access to your mobile device's address book (collectively, "Personal Information"). 

Your phone number, which will be verified via a text message that will be sent to you or phone verification, will be used for identification purposes as your MobileVOIP user ID. 

MobileVOIP works with Crashlytics, Inc ("Crashlytics") to report any bug affecting our iOS and Android Apps. If either app crashes during normal use, the app will send certain information about the incident to Crashlytics. This information consists of the device type, OS version and certain hardware information about your mobile device, and the time of the crash, the state of the application at the time of the crash, and stack traces. [Click here](https://try.crashlytics.com/terms/privacy-policy.pdf) to review Crashlytics' privacy policy. 

**Third-Party Sites and Privacy Practices**  
You may arrive at our Site and/or download the MobileVOIP App from another website. In addition, our Site may contain links that will let you leave our Site and access another website. Websites linked to or from our Site are not under the control of MobileVOIP and it is possible that these websites have a different privacy policy. Our Policy applies solely to Personal Information that is acquired through your use of our Services, and/or your relationship with MobileVOIP. We urge you to be careful when you enter any personal information online. 

**Analytics Collection**  
MobileVOIP uses Google Analytics to help us anonymously track and report user/visitor behavior information and users’ standard log information to the Site. This information (including but not limited to: IP address, data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and information processing) helps us analyze and evaluate how the Site is used as part of our ongoing efforts to improve the Site and App’s features and services. No personally identifying data is included in this type of reporting. Google Analytics may have access to your information only for the purposes of performing these tasks and on behalf of MobileVOIP and under obligation similar in those in this Privacy Policy. For more information about the terms that govern Google Analytics, please visit the [Google Analytics terms of service](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html). 

We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source. 

  2. **Security**  
We take reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although we cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, we have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in place to protect Personal Information. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. 

  3. **Changes to Policy** From time to time, we may revise this Policy. We reserve the right to update or modify this Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time with or without notice. We will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information we collect, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. You agree to review the Policy periodically so that you are aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to any changes and signifies your agreement to the terms of our Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use the Site, the MobileVOIP App, or any of the other Services.
